JUAN PABLO PECH QUIJANO

SYSTEM ENGINEER

+52 9871034376

Mexico

juan_p@live.com.mx

ABOUT ME

Passionate of the technology, Always I attempt to be better every day. I'm an honest person, creative when I try to solve problems, I have experience working as part of a team, I'm in continual training on my own, learning something new about new technologies or improving my knowledge.

EDUCATION

High School

Instituto tecnológico de Mérida

CISCO CCNA R&S Certificate

System engineer

2014 - 2017

2018 - 2022

EXPERTISE

Angular development.

Web development with HTML, CSS,

JavaScript.

Development with C#.

Azure.

Knowledge in Java web development.

Networking installation.

Project documentation.

EXPERIENCE

Web apps developer

Jan 2020 - Aug 2022

Celulas Plenum by Plenumsoft

Took part from the beginning in an internal project of the company, using the technologies like Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript as frontend and C# with .Net Core framework for the backend and Microsoft SQL server for the database implementation, using the SCRUM methodology.

Computer maintenance and fixing.

Aug 2011 - Dec 2016

Simple Web

- -Software installation.
- -Laptops and computers fix and maintenance.

CERTIFICATION

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals AZ-900

Innovaccion Virtual

Dec 2021

COURSES

Websites programing

CENTRO DE CAPACITACIÓN PARA ELTRABAJO INDUSTRIAL NUM. 30

Aug 2020 - Dec 2020

Full stack developer

Launch X Innovaccion Virtual by Microsoft

Mar 2022 - May 2022

